Colorado
Marist College
Colorado
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.1.4
1203 linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Colorado
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - Colorado, 2.1.1.1.4
              - Stanley Hotel Manor and amusement hall, Estes Park, 1911; 20 (Box 1175)
                5x7
              - In front of Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 21
              - Stanley Hotel from hill opposite Estes Park, 1911; 22
              - Stanley Hotel music room, Estes Park, 1911; 23
              - Stanley Manor music room, Estes Park, 1911; 24
              - Stanley Manor music room, Estes Park, 1911; 25
              - Bedroom, Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 26
              - Dining room, Stanley Manor, Estes Park, 1911; 27
              - Hall in Stanley Manor, Estes Park, 1911; 28
              - Rocks near Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 29
              - Rocks behind Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 30
              - Fireplace in main building, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 31
              - Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 32
              - Mill's house, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 33
              - Rooms in Mrs. Sherman's cottage, Estes Park, 1911; 34
              - Frank R. Roberson and party at Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 35
              - The Forest at Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 36
              - Porch of "the forest", Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 37
              - Main building, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 38
              - Mr. Enos Mills, Estes Park, 1911; 39
              - Dorothy Schwartz, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 40
              - Party at castle rocks, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 41
              - Park on castle rocks, Long's PeaK, Estes Park, 1911; 42
              - Frank R. Roberson and party on castle rocks, near view, Estes Park, 1911; 43
              - Beaver dam, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 44
              - Beaver work on trees, Estes Park, 1911; 45
              - Beaver dam near Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 46
              - Showing how a tree cured itself, Estes Park, 1911; 47
              - Mertensia orchid, lungwort, Estes Park, 1911; 48
              - Purple bell flower, clematis, Estes Park, 1911; 49
              - Lupinus, Estes Park, 1911; 50
              - Larkspur ans yellow orange flower, Estes Park, 1911; 1 (Box 1176)
              - Kinnikinick, Estes Park, 1911; 2
              - Potentilla climbing, Estes Park, 1911; 3
              - Pine cones, Estes Park, 1911; 4
              - Big Thompson Canyon, river and road, Estes Park, 1911; 5
              - Big Thomson Canyon, island in river, Estes Park, 1911; 6
              - Stream in Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 7
              - Bridge in Bid Thomson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 8
              - Bridge in the canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 9
              - Big Thomson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 10
              - Lyons Canyon road, Estes Park, 1911; 11
              - Route through Missouri Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 12
              - Range from Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 13
              - Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 14
              - General view of Estes Park, 1911; 15
              - General view of Estes Park, taken from mountain near entrance, 1911; 16
              - Looking into Estes Park from mountain near entrance, 1911; 17
              - Ypsilon mountain, Estes Park, 1911; 18
              - Range from Park Hill, Estes Park, 1911; 19
              - Range from Park Hill, Estes Park, 1911; 20
              - Range from Mr. Lanborn's house[?], Estes Park, 1911; 21
              - Mountain range, Long's Peak Inn to left Estes Park, 1911; 22
              - Estes Park, 1911; 23
              - Cabin in the woods, Estes Park, 1911; 24
              - Cottages among trees, Estes Park, 1911; 25
              - Deer mountain in the distance, Estes Park, 1911; 26
              - Song's Peak, Estes Park, 1911; 27
              - Beaver dam, Estes Park, 1911; 28
                4x5
              - The fish hatchery, Estes Park, 1911; 29
              - Trout in pond, Estes Park, 1911; 30
              - Enos Mills feeding chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 31
              - Frank R. Roberson and chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 32
              - Mr. Enos Mills and a chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 33
              - Mr. Lamborne and Bevis(dog), Estes Park, 1911; 34
              - Lake and trees, Estes Park, 1911; 35
              - Bevis(a dog), Estes Park, 1911; 36
              - Bevis waiting for sugar, Estes Park, 1911; 37
              - Children on horseback, Estes Park, 1911; 38
              - Donkeys, Estes Park, 1911; 39
              - Johnny Adam's cabin, Estes Park, 1911; 40
              - Mr. and Mrs. Lamborne, Estes Park, 1911; 41
              - Mr. Lester, proprietor of the Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 42
              - Johnny Adams, Estes Park, 1911; 43
              - Fishing in Big Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 44
              - Canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 45
              - Narrow defile[?], Big Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 46
              - Fisherman in the canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 47
              - Fishing in the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 48
              - Road and river,canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 49
              - Trout fishing in Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 50
              - Flower, potentilla?, Estes Park, 1911; 51
              - Blue bell flower, clematis douglasii, Estes Park, 1911; 52
              - Flowers, erigeron (probably) poliospermum, Estes Park, 1911; 53
              - Iris, missouriensis, Estes Park, 1911; 54
              - Flowers, Estes Park, 1911; 1 (Box 1177)
              - Flowers, Estes Park, 1911; 2
              - Yellow flower, Estes Park, 1911; 3
              - Range of mountains, Estes Park, 1911; 4
              - Entrance to Estes Park, 1911; 5
              - Long's Peak, Estes Park, 1911; 6
              - Road to Mr. Mills, Estes Park, 1911; 7
              - Road to Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 8
              - Deer Mountain Drive, Estes Park, 1911; 9
              - Road on Deer Mountain Drive, Estes Park, 1911; 10
              - Lyon's Canyon Road, Estes Park, 1911; 11
              - School house, Estes Park, 1911; 12
              - Balanced rock, Estes Park, 1911; 13
              - Denver at night, showing electric building, 1911; 14
              - Denver at night, showing auditorium, 1911; 15
              - Denver at night, looking up the 16th Street, 1911; 16
              - Denver at night, 1911; 17
              - Denver at night, 1911; 18
              - Main Street, Fort Collins, 1911; 19
              - Bank Interior, Fort Collins, 1911; 20
              - Lover's lane, Fort Collins, 1911; 21
              - Residence, Fort Collins, 1911; 22
              - Y.M.C.A., Fort Collins, 1911; 23
              - Interior of Y.M.C.A., Fort Collins, 1911; 24
              - Business section of town, Fort Collins, 1911; 25
              - Street, Fort Collins, 1911; 26
              - Agriculture college, Fort Collins, 1911; 27